<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Georgiy Mogelashvili</title>
    <link>http://glamcoder.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Georgiy Mogelashvili</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 23:33:07 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://glamcoder.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://glamcoder.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 23:33:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://glamcoder.org/about/</guid>
      <description>In his 10+ years experience Georgiy had a chance to work for small local companies, country scale enterprises, non-profit organisations and international corporations.
Today Georgiy is working at Booking.com, world&amp;rsquo;s leading online travel agency. His role there - Senior Developer and Team Lead, and he is responsible for company products development as well as people management.
Georgiy believes that main skill each manager should have is openness - ability to honestly and fairly talk to your direct reports and people around you in order to achieve results together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Russian] Быть лидером, а не боссом. Автономия и Servant Leadership в управлении командами.</title>
      <link>http://glamcoder.org/conferences/codefest-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://glamcoder.org/conferences/codefest-2018/</guid>
      <description>https://2018.codefest.ru/lecture/1247/
Быть лидером, а не боссом. Эта простая фраза известна всем, и воспринимается как должное. Однако же в жизни нередки случаи, когда тимлид в твоей команде берет на себя всю ответственность и все решения, не оставляя никакой свободы своим подчинённым.
Такое было и в Booking.com некоторое время назад. Роль тимлида подразумевала полную ответственность за команду и процессы - работа с трекерами, организация митингов (планирования, ретроспектив и тп), работа с людьми.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Russian] Из закрытой касты в Servant Leader - эволюция тимлида в Booking.com</title>
      <link>http://glamcoder.org/conferences/teamleadconf-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://glamcoder.org/conferences/teamleadconf-2018/</guid>
      <description>http://teamleadconf.ru/2018/abstracts/3168
Компания Booking.com существует уже больше 20 лет. За это время она выросла от небольшого голландского стартапа до крупной международной корпорации, лидера на рынке онлайн путешествий, с офисами по всему миру.
За последние несколько лет Booking.com увеличил количество сотрудников в IT департаменте. И это повлекло за собой изменения в роли тимлида. Мы прошли путь от причастности тимлида к ограниченному кругу людей (&amp;ldquo;касте&amp;rdquo;), частичного отказа от лидов на какое-то время в пользу автономных команд, и до их возвращения под новой концепцией &amp;ldquo;Servant Leader&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A/B test with azure websites traffic routing</title>
      <link>http://glamcoder.org/conferences/cloudbrew-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://glamcoder.org/conferences/cloudbrew-2015/</guid>
      <description>http://www.cloudbrew.be/2015/
Do you have a website? If yes then how do you test ideas that you want to implement? What if your brand new solution will ruin user experience? And what if you have a critical bug being deployed to production? From this talk you will know how to A/B test your web applications more confidently and safely with new Azure Websites Traffic Routing services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to do A/B tests with Azure Websites Traffic Routing</title>
      <link>http://glamcoder.org/conferences/topconf-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://glamcoder.org/conferences/topconf-2015/</guid>
      <description>Do you have a website? If yes then how do you test ideas that you want to implement? What if your brand new solution will ruin user experience? And what if you have a critical bug being deployed to production? From this talk you will know how to A/B test your web applications more confidently and safely with new Azure Websites Traffic Routing services.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A/B test with azure websites traffic routing</title>
      <link>http://glamcoder.org/conferences/devdaykyiv-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://glamcoder.org/conferences/devdaykyiv-2015/</guid>
      <description>https://devday.in.ua/#program
Do you have a website? If yes then how do you test ideas that you want to implement? What if your brand new solution will ruin user experience? And what if you have a critical bug being deployed to production? From this talk you will know how to A/B test your web applications more confidently and safely with new Azure Websites Traffic Routing services.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GTA: How to make your visitors Get The App</title>
      <link>http://glamcoder.org/conferences/mobileappeurope-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://glamcoder.org/conferences/mobileappeurope-2015/</guid>
      <description>Mobile apps become more and more significant part of our life. There are already &amp;ldquo;apps only&amp;rdquo; hyper-popular services like Instagram or Uber. If you have a website but also a mobile app, some day you might end up loosing your users if you won&amp;rsquo;t advertise your app properly on your website. During this talk I will demonstrate you some techniques we use at Booking.com to make our visitors Get The App.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web site cloud A/B testing - why, how and what to do with it</title>
      <link>http://glamcoder.org/conferences/devcon-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://glamcoder.org/conferences/devcon-2015/</guid>
      <description>Users will probably not feel happy about every single developer&amp;rsquo;s solution implemented in your web site. Make decision-making more reliable leveraging A/B testing. During this presentation you will learn what is it, how to configure A/B tests in Microsoft Azure cloud simply and quickly, and then analyze the results on the example of a small project.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Russian] Мастер-класс: Облачный бекенд для мобильных устройств своими руками</title>
      <link>http://glamcoder.org/conferences/codefest-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://glamcoder.org/conferences/codefest-2014/</guid>
      <description>https://2014.codefest.ru/lecture/975/
На этом мастер-классе вы сможете научиться работать с облачными технологиями и самостоятельно добавить в свое мобильное приложение такие полезные вещи, как: авторизация через соц сети, push-уведомления и облачный бекенд. Причем не только для Windows!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Russian] Мобильные сервисы, блобы и Windows 8. Храним данные в Windows Azure</title>
      <link>http://glamcoder.org/conferences/codefest-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2013 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://glamcoder.org/conferences/codefest-2013/</guid>
      <description>https://2013.codefest.ru/lecture/51/
В докладе будет на практическом примере рассказано о двух способах хранения данных мобильного приложения в Windows Azure. Для больших и редкоиспользуемых данных будет использоваться Azure Blob Storage, в то время как для данных мелкого объема мы воспользуемся Windows Azure Mobile Services. На примере приложения для Windows 8 и Windows Phone 8 будет показан способ работы с этими хранилищами с помощью .NET SDK и веб-сервисов.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>